<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>H9</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/content/</link>
    <description>Recent content on H9</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© H9</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 23:15:36 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/content/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Wani Ctf 2024 Writeup</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/content/wani-ctf/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 23:15:36 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/content/wani-ctf/</guid>
      <description>This is my writeup for Wani CTF&#xA;Forensics Surveillance of sus A binary file is given, and after some investigation, it has a RDP8BMP Header.&#xA;To get the BMP images, I have referred to this article and use a Python Script (bmc-tools).&#xA;After all the bmp files are recovered, the flag can be readed in plain sight if the view is changed to &amp;ldquo;Large icons&amp;rdquo;.&#xA;Flag : FLAG{RDP_is_useful_yipeee}&#xA;Tiny USB A disk image file is given.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>VSCTF Awa-Jelly Writeup</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/content/vsctf/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 11:32:57 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/content/vsctf/</guid>
      <description>For this CTF, I only solved one question by myself, so here is the writeup for awa-jelly (reverse engineering)&#xA;Hello&#xA;Basically, the challenge is to recover the redacted input text so that the output is same as displayed.&#xA;Although I know Python a little, I decided to use the traditional method: Excel 🤦🏻&#xA;Throughout my process, I tried to recover the scrambling algorithm by using Python, and I discovered some characters cannot be displayed after scrambling, which caused my natural approach to be weird due to some characters are missing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Typography</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/content/post-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Mar 2018 12:13:38 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/content/post-5/</guid>
      <description>Lid est laborum et dolorum fuga. Et harum quidem rerum facilis est et expeditasi distinctio. Nam libero tempore, cum soluta nobis est eligendi optio cumque nihilse impedit quo minus id quod amets untra dolor amet sad. Sed ut perspser iciatis unde omnis iste natus error sit voluptatem accusantium doloremque laste. Dolores sadips ipsums sits.&#xA;Heading 1 Lid est laborum et dolorum fuga. Et harum quidem rerum facilis est et expeditasi distinctio.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
